{
    "id": "328e113f93ed4beb873535392ba2adb1",
    "title": "Conjunctions and relative pronouns: grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "44c4f55d5581437cbaca23c7beec6872",
            "title": "Conjunctions And Relative Pronouns",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "It is a question ............................................ nobody can answer.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "which",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I stayed an extra night ............................................... I could see Merlin.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "such that",
                        "so that",
                        "that"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "...................................................... I was having a shower, I slipped on the floor.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Whereas",
                        "Since",
                        "While"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "..................................................... she was too angry to speak, Alice said nothing.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "As",
                        "Because",
                        "Since",
                        "All of the above"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................................ the coat was expensive, I bought it.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Although",
                        "Though",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The house ............................................... I live is very small.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "where",
                        "there",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will always remember the day ................................................ I first met you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "when",
                        "that",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have got a friend ........................................... serves in the army.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "which",
                        "when"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Cook slowly ..................................................... it is ready.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "until",
                        "till",
                        "up to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................................... I will have time I am not sure at the moment.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Whether",
                        "Unless",
                        "Weather"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}